<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mobilei Assist</string>
    <string name="title_activity_to_do">ToDoActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="Login_text">If you don\'t have an account click here to create one</string>
    <string name="clearHistory">Long press item to delete permanently</string>
    <string name="home_text">MOBILEi ASSIST</string>
    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="search_history">Search History</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="about_paragraph">GPA means Grade Point Average. The GPA is a system of judging a student’s performance and it followed throughout the world.If a student seeking admission to graduate studies has grades in a different system he or she should clearly mention that GPA system does not exist and provide details on the system. In the event of a system different from the usual GPA system, some universities may ask for a detailed method of evaluation of the scores with their scales</string>
    <string name="about_paragraph2">In such case consult the Registrar or controller of examination of the University for an official evaluation to be included along with the transcripts. It is recommended to send your rank certification or official average score of class/ toppers grades etc..to ease the difference between GPA and your system.GPA is one of the most important factors to get admission in a good college.
Each course is given a certain number of “units” or “credits”, depending on the content of the course. In secondary school, most course carry the same number of units, but this is not true at the college level.</string>
    
</resources>
